- Ready, set, go!
- Gentle-hearted gay man Genichi Hatano
and his partner Saku Sakuta
begin searching for a home
to serve as a "clamp".
I want to make guitars.
Hotaru finally discovers
something she truly loves.
The trio’s "Parent-Child Contract"
continues.
- But then,
- It's a tortoise.
- Genichi’s pet tortoise escapes,
- Mr. Hatano?
and when he reports it to the police,
things start to take a sketchy turn.
Genichi then ends up
being taken in by the police.
SUGINAMI CENTRAL POLICE
This way.
First time in a police car?
Yes.
I figured getting you here fast
would be best.
I didn’t expect to come in a police car.
The little tortoise looked miserable.
I’m just glad you found it.
- This is ridiculous.
- Huh?
Picking someone up in a police car?
That just isn't right.
- Figured.
- Come on. You were out on patrol anyway.
We’ll get in trouble for this.
- Oh, and speaking of which, Mr. Hatano…
- What?
You wrote your stage name
on the lost tortoise report, right?
That’ll get you in trouble!
Oh, I didn’t even realize.
I usually write my real name,
not my stage name.
What stage name?
Mr. Hatano here used to aim
to become a musician
and still goes by that stage name,
which is Genichi Hatano.
His real name is Mr. Jin Ichigaya.
- Ah, you’ve got your ID, right?
- Huh?
You’ll need it when picking up
your tortoise.
I can do the explanation
about your stage name.
Oh, no. I know you’re busy, Ms. Matsu.
Really, I'm fine by myself.
Ah, no worries.
It'll be quick anyway. This way.
No, no, no. I can do this myself, really.
Thank you. Sorry for the trouble.
What?
I thought he was busted.
Him pretending to be my parent and all.
He just went to pick up his tortoise.
We won't be arrested if caught, right?
"Could be charged
with violation of Child Welfare Act,
youth protection law,
local development ordinance,
or Minor Offenses Act."
So, we may become serious criminals?
- Did you manage to pick it up properly?
- Yes.
Thank you. I'll be leaving now.
The person with the tortoise earlier…
Ah, yes. Mr. Genichi Hatano.
Was the ID name the same?
- His ID.
- Yes.
I'm back.
Good thing you found it.
It might not be, actually.
Why?
Well…
Ms. Matsu might’ve figured something out.
It's fine. If they find out,
I’ll explain everything.
I’ll beg them to not arrest you,
Mr. Hatano.
I'll get arrested?
I’ll appeal to them too
that you're not a criminal.
I'm a criminal?
I’m your accomplice anyway.
- Sakuta…
- Yes?
Let's break up.
Huh?
Because you're a teacher.
And Hotaru,
you can just blame it all on me.
- No!
- Are you stupid?
- That's mean.
- Which of us is being mean here?
Say "let’s break up" one more time,
and we're done for good.
No. I don't want that.
Then I don't want to hear that
from you ever again.
Okay. I'm sorry.
You’re terrible at staking out,
you know, Ms. Matsu?
You're in the open.
- Ms. Inokashira.
- Yes?
Were you aware of it?
About what?
Genichi Hatano…
He isn’t Hotaru Kusunoki’s father, is he?
Lying or hiding information
can lead to charges, just so you know.
Okay.
Were you pretending
to be Hotaru’s guardian too?
Not at all.
You and Mr. Sakuta turned a blind eye
to the fact that Mr. Hatano
was acting as her parent, right?
Yes.
- Did Hotaru give you anything in return?
- No.
Are you in contact with her mom?
Yes and no.
Do you know
where the embezzled money went?
Yes and no.
Well, if you’re hiding money for her,
that’s definitely a crime.
About Hotaru,
is there any chance Mr. Hatano
is abusing or threatening her?
Not at all.
How can you be so sure?
You can tell just by watching them.
But sometimes you can’t, right?
But first, you’ve got
to actually observe, right?
For example, their eyes can sometimes look
almond-shaped or perfectly round.
Or you may notice that the insides
of their ears and noses are a cute pink.
Even the unexpected things
become clear if you really pay attention.
What are you talking about?
It’s about goats.
Why goats?
Oh, right!
Want this? I’ll lend it to you.
Do you think Hatano will get arrested?
Hard to say.
Keep today’s discussion between us.
For legal reasons, you know.
Yes and no.
You told her everything?
Her pressure was insane. What could I do?
The police really are something.
Even about my mom?
I told her "yes and no" for that.
What?
I gave an ambiguous answer
to skate things around.
Don’t let Hatano know about this.
If he finds out, he’ll probably
do something unnecessary.
Leave Ms. Matsu to me, then.
What do you mean?
Aren't you excited?
You mean, for Christmas?
For the reserved cake.
Ah, right. I need to pick it up.
Yeah.
How is it?
What are you doing here?
- I’m assisting the investigation.
- No, thanks.
- I’ll just talk to them directly.
- Wait!
Observe properly first.
If you do, you’ll understand.
Trust me.
What are they to each other?
Isn’t it obvious from what you see?
- Partners in crime?
- You should go with just what you see.
MILK
He grabbed the milk from the front
and put it in the basket.
Would a bad person
really take milk from the front?
I hope Koito and his partner made up.
I’m sure they did!
Aren’t you standing really close?
We’re partners, remember?
Well, yeah.
We should think about
that kind of stuff too, you know.
What?
About what to put in a notarized contract.
Things like property,
or what happens if we get sick…
Let's leave that to the professionals.
More like how Koito and his partner
have their "hard-boiled egg" rule.
For example, "always drink milk
in the morning"?
I drink coffee.
Noted.
Why don’t we try doing a simulation?
A simulation?
Nice!
What's your verdict?
They’re…
building something?
What are you doing?
Yes?
You were staring…
at the kids. Am I wrong?
I’m with the police. My name is Matsu.
I’m the landlady, Inokashira.
Oh? From that apartment
where I had the roasted sweet potatoes?
- Thank you for coming.
- Don't mention it.
Why are you with the police, landlady?
You are…?
I’m with an organization called Nikomado.
My name is Koito.
I see.
- And you know those kids?
- Yeah.
They’re always around.
- Thank you for looking after her.
- Don't mention it.
They’re… handcrafting something.
Not what you expected?
People call them "Toyoko Kids",
but of course, there’s no one
actually by that name.
Even if they’re in the same place,
they’re all different kids.
Naturally, there are also kids
who are just having fun.
I’m heading back for now.
‪If you'd excuse me.
See you.
RESERVATION SLIP
Have you made any reservations recently?
Recently… No.
- Why not?
- There’s just been too much going on.
Sorry about this.
TOOTHPASTE
Okay then,
for drafting the notarized contract,
we’ll start the joint-living simulation.
I appreciate the cooperation.
No problem.
Um, what should we do?
Shall we cook a meal?
Yeah. Then…
- Curry!
- How about stew?
KOKUUMA CREAM STEW, KOKUUMA CURRY
You're fine with stew?
I’m older, so I’ll yield to you.
Huh?
Hey!
Stop worrying about your age!
I'm sorry.
Good.
We can write "no worrying about age"
on the notarized contract.
There's no need to write that!
I'm sorry.
Good.
What dish is this, exactly?
Does it have a name?
Curry Cream Stew? Cream Stew Curry?
- Let's dig in.
- Yeah.
It's delicious!
- Good morning.
- Sorry for doing this without asking…
- Not at all.
I toasted some bread. Want some?
Yeah, sure.
- You drink milk, right?
- Ah, yes.
- Wait.
- Huh?
How about a café au lait?
Sounds good.
MILK
Today, let’s try simulating
an actual budget for buying a house
and see what we get.
Based on that,
I'll find you appropriate properties.
Okay.
We’re actually doing
a simulation right now too.
- What simulation?
- Our cohabitation life.
Wow, you two are so lovey-dovey!
I’m really happy for you!
I feel like I might cry.
You're being over the top.
Well, we're lovey-dovey, though.
Um, could we start the budget simulation?
Sorry.
First, you two want a joint loan, yes?
That's right. We want it
in both our names,
so we’re both responsible.
We want to split it evenly too,
and each own the house 50/50.
Very well. Then let’s start
with your annual income.
- About 4.5 million.
- 6.5 million yen.
What, really?
I think that's about right.
Ah…
I feel kind of pathetic, you know?
Judging someone by how much money
they make is so outdated.
I'm sorry.
We can write "no grudges over money"
in the notarized contract.
- There's no need for that.
- Okay.
By the way, for the loan period,
the maximum age is 80.
Based on Genichi’s age,
we could manage at most…
30 years.
It's all because I'm so old…
Stop worrying about your age!
We should write this
in the notarized contract aft--
- I said no!
- Okay.
- Sorry.
- No worries.
Alright, what about monthly repayments?
Would around 150,000 yen be the limit?
That’s 75,000 yen each.
Based on that, a rough estimate
of the maximum loan amount
is 51 million yen.
How much are you thinking
for down payment?
About two million each,
as we discussed the other day.
- Yes.
- So, that adds up to 55 million yen.
Properties around this range
would be appropriate.
- Fifty-five million yen, huh…
- Give me a moment.
Recommendations within your budget…
Here are a few.
Let's see…
What do you think?
Let's try putting
the budget aside for a bit
and start with the conditions first.
Sure, no problem.
- Start with the area you want to live in.
- Within the 23 wards of Tokyo?
I’d like it to be close to work,
so this area would be good.
What about size?
Around 60 square meters is ideal.
The dogs will be with us too,
and we’d like separate rooms.
Sixty square meters, 2LDK,
and pet-friendly.
And within a 15-minute walk
from the station.
I’d like the place
to be less than ten years old.
Oh, and a parking lot.
Got it.
And, if possible, one more room.
Right.
Understood.
Please give me a moment.
Have a look.
- Let's see…
- Take your time.
75,800,000 YEN
So expensive.
80,800,000 YEN
You guys need to be realistic.
- Did you sleep well?
- Yes.
This is today's breakfast.
Thank you.
Sakuta has been making it lately.
- Good morning.
- Why are you here again?
I might have a talent for tailing people.
What?
Never mind that. Just observe carefully.
- Don't tell him, okay?
- So, you prefer dried sardine rice ball?
- See you.
Okay, let's go.
So, how was it? Do you get it now
after observing thoroughly?
Picking the milk in front…
Having fun…
Seeing her off…
It was all normal.
- See?
- But I don't get it.
- Huh?
- You know,
I think sometimes just observing
isn’t enough to understand.
Well, thank you for your cooperation
in the investigation. If you'd excuse me.
After deducting handling fees,
that comes to 123,000 yen.
If you’re fine with that, please sign
and seal here.
Mr. Ichigaya?
Yes?
I'll do it, yeah!
JIN ICHIGAYA
I didn’t have a choice.
I didn’t want to sell it either,
but supporting this little guy
isn’t cheap.
So, you’re looking for a new place
to start fresh?
Somewhere cheap where I can live
with him. Somewhere decent.
In that case,
the one I showed you before
is the only place I can recommend.
I don’t want to live in such a place.
Is that so?
For now…
I guess I can check it out.
Understood.
INOKASHIRA APARTMENTS VIEWING
FOR MR. ICHIGAYA
FOR THURSDAY THE 25TH
I wonder if there’s a school
that teaches how to make guitars.
What made you want to make guitars?
I don't know.
Right.
So, I thought, maybe I’ll try making one.
That sounds fun.
Not that I’m gonna show anyone,
even if it’s finished.
What, not even to Hatano?
Nope.
He'd cry. I'm telling you!
I’ll do some research on my end too.
Thank you.
Mr. Sakuta.
So, there’s no doubt
you helped Mr. Hatano?
Yes.
Why did you?
I wonder why myself.
As a teacher, that’s already wrong.
But what would the right thing
for a teacher to do be?
Mr. Sakuta,
why did you want to become a teacher?
There was this science teacher
whose little stories were fun.
The way he explained the concept of time…
He said that the passage of time
is like things mixing together.
Like how coffee and milk mix
into café au lait.
Once they mix, they don’t separate again.
That’s what time is.
Learning things
you don’t understand is fascinating.
So, you looked up to that teacher
and decided to be one?
I also thought…
there should be a variety of teachers.
What do you mean?
Such as teachers who don't like school,
teachers who aren't good at teaching,
and teachers who feel uncomfortable
in the classroom.
Even teachers who are gay.
With Mr. Hatano…
Are you dating him?
I know you’ve been keeping an eye
on us the whole time.
You’re not very good at stakeouts.
But I think it’s okay
to have clumsy police officers too.
I’ll report back
to the school another day.
Okay.
So, what did you think of the place
after checking it out?
It satisfies most of your criteria.
I’m not sure anymore.
- Huh?
- I’ve seen so many places
that I’m forgetting
what really matters to me.
What kind of home
do I actually want to live in?
Why don't you try
a different perspective for once?
What do you mean?
Let’s see some properties
that don’t match your criteria at all.
Okay, let's do just that.
Very well.
INOKASHIRA APARTMENTS VIEWING
FOR MS. MOMOSE
Done!
- We did it!
- Yay!
Well then,
- I'm going to play it.
- Okay.
Wow!
- You're amazing!
- It does produce sounds!
It's kinda funny.
- This is a masterpiece.
- You're the best.
Look over here, Hotaru!
It's kinda cool!
Does Coffee catch your eye?
- What?
- Ah, my bad.
That’s the name of this guitar.
Because it’s made
with the color of coffee,
they call it Coffee.
I didn't know guitars actually have names.
This one’s called Cherry.
It's made using cherry blossom wood.
That over there is Maple.
They're all made
by the same guitar workshop,
but they give them these unique names.
What about yours?
What do you call it?
Today my heart
Tucked in the bottom of my bag
Hid…
- Um!
- Yes?
There's something…
What?
I noticed something during our simulation.
Okay.
Your singing.
What, you hate music?
No, I love it.
And I guess because I do…
I don’t mind listening
to your singing, Hatano.
But anything else, it distracts me…
No, that’s not quite right.
It makes my feelings all over the place.
Sorry.
I'm happy to hear that.
- Huh?
- Because you don’t
really talk much about yourself.
I'm just not good at it.
So,
living together and getting to know you
makes me really, really happy.
So, when I want to sing,
I’ll ask if it’s alright with you, okay?
Are there certain times
you feel like singing?
Yeah. All sorts of times.
When I want to understand
my own feelings, I guess?
What do you mean?
I realized that back during my first love,
I used to write songs too.
That’s how I knew I was in love!
When you understand your own feelings,
it puts you at ease.
Welcome!
You’re in luck!
- Huh?
- We still have Christmas cakes.
Well, uh…
I'm sure your wife
or kids would be pleased!
Oh, that’s good. Lucky me, really.
That's right…
I also recommend this one.
It even has floor heating.
Will floor heating make me happy?
To some extent.
Warm floors do make life a little happier.
I’ve just been feeling…
unsettled lately.
- Is that so?
- Even though I’m single…
I went and bought a huge cake.
You get to enjoy a whole cake on your own!
Ah, sorry.
That’s probably not what you meant.
How do I find my happiness?
Tomorrow, I’m going to check out
an interesting property.
You may find something
while looking at different places.
Maybe even what you consider happiness.
Then, I’ll leave it to you.
Okay.
INOKASHIRA APARTMENTS VIEWING
FOR MR. YOSHIDA
INOKASHIRA APARTMENTS
Hello.
- This is the apartment we'll be viewing.
- Right.
Mr. Yoshida.
- Mr. Yoshida is tagging along as well?
- Um…
- Is this the place?
- Yes.
It's called Inokashira Apartments.
This place might not be
the one for me. Sorry.
Wait, why?
- Ah!
- Uh…
Everyone!
Welcome!
This is the landlady, Ms. Inokashira.
- This is Mr. Yoshida…
- Mr. Yoshida, nice to meet you.
Likewise.
I'm Momose. Nice to meet you.
Ah, you're from the parfait place!
Ah, you're from that day!
Thank you for that day.
- You know each other?
- Yes.
I see.
There's one more person.
It's this person.
You're from that day.
Hello.
So, you’ve decided to look after Hotaru?
You know each other too?
He's Kusunoki's dad.
- What?
- Who's Kusunoki?
You're from the stakeout!
What stakeout? Why?
- She's with the police.
- What?
- Is there a case?
- Hello.
Hello.
I'm hoping we can properly speak today.
Okay. Right this way, please.
What?
What case is this about?
Stakeout?
What do you mean by that?
Coming!
- Hello.
- Huh?
- What's going on?
- Mr. Hatano?
Genichi, did you do something?
Genichi Hatano.
I came by to hear what you have to say.
And since you all appear
to know one another,
would it be alright
if I spoke with you collectively?
I'm Matsu from Suginami Central Police,
Community Safety Division.
For the past few days,
I’ve been looking into Mr. Hatano
and those around him.
What?
Ms. Inokashira
and Mr. Sakuta,
I've already spoken to them.
You knew about this?
Yes.
Mr. Hatano.
You’re pretending
to be Hotaru Kusunoki’s dad,
is that right?
- Yes.
- Kusunoki is only 15 years old, a minor.
Since there could be a case involved,
we’ve been investigating.
Now, starting from you.
Please tell me about your relationship
with Mr. Hatano.
My name is Okabe.
I'm Genichi’s friend
and a property agent.
My name is Momose.
Can I tell her about that?
Well, yes.
I'm a consultant at a partner agency.
What's that?
It's a marriage consultation agency
for gay people.
I see.
And you are?
Please be honest.
Is it okay to say it too?
It's fine.
If you're okay with it.
My name is Yoshida.
Uh…
He's my ex-boyfriend,
and he's his current boyfriend.
- Wait, what?
- Oh, I see how it is.
A love triangle?
Is that true?
We've already broken up amicably.
So,
did you know about Mr. Hatano
and Kusunoki’s relationship?
I've heard about it briefly.
They're really not involved in this.
Why did you do this?
I asked him to.
Really?
He isn’t making you say this?
I’m speaking for myself.
Has he done anything you didn’t like?
He made dinner for me without asking,
helped me prepare for my test,
and nagged about me being home late.
I didn’t like those things.
Even if it was purely for Hotaru’s sake,
there were other ways to handle it, no?
So, why did you go out of your way
to pretend to be her parent?
Did you want to try raising a child?
- Huh?
- Because the two of you…
can’t have one, yes?
Ms. Matsu!
I apologize if I come off as rude,
but what’s the truth of it?
I can’t say for sure that…
that wasn’t the case.
So, that was your intention, then?
- Is that a bad thing?
- What?
It doesn’t matter
what Mr. Hatano’s motives were.
I appreciated his help.
I’m just glad about that.
Maybe that’s true for now.
No matter what happens from here on,
I’ll feel the same. I'm sure about it.
You can’t really know that, can you?
Uh, Genichi is just a meddling,
music-loving old man.
I agree! Saku
has a good eye for men,
and he’s with this person.
What do you mean?
Um…
Love and revolution!
- Huh?
- I think why Mr. Hatano and the others
acted as her parents
was probably for love and revolution.
What's that?
I'm not sure how to explain it. Um…
Love…
is like finding someone
or something you care about.
And rebelling against people who try
to push you around, or society in general,
and then becoming free,
living life the way you want.
- I don't really get it.
- In any case,
we live for love and revolution!
What a cool thing to say!
Oh, no. Please stop.
The one that's cool is Dazai.
Love and revolution, huh?
LOVE AND REVOLUTION
Will Mr. Hatano be arrested?
If what everyone here said is true,
then probably no.
He hasn’t done anything wrong
to you, Hotaru.
Thank goodness…
But he will be questioned voluntarily,
and, of course, the school
and child guidance center
will be notified.
Why is that?
I’m fine with this,
and so is Mr. Hatano and Mr. Sakuta.
They're fine with it.
What if you were to get sick
in the future?
Or during exams, when you need
to fill out important documents?
Think about it realistically.
Right now, relying properly
on the systems in place
is far safer and more reassuring.
This is so you won’t suffer later.
Please rely on them.
That’s what I’m here for.
Um…
Yes?
Let’s break up, Sakuta.
- What?
- Huh?
I said if you say that again,
I’d really break up, didn't I?
Yes.
You're okay with that?
- That can't be good.
- Yeah.
That's not good.
I'm okay with it.
Sakuta…
I don’t want you
to be held responsible at school.
Neither do I want you
to be questioned by the police.
It’s all my fault.
Please break up with me.
I did this because I wanted to.
Sakuta and I…
are strangers.
We're not married and can never be.
So, please do not mention his name
to the police, the school, or anyone else.
I'm begging you!
- Well…
- Please!
Um…
That's all you need to know
for today, am I right?
- Yes.
- We will excuse ourselves now.
What?
Hey!
Is this my fault?
- Just get in!
- Okay.
Um…
I was thinking
if there’s anything I can do to help.
Sorry, this is our problem.
- Okay.
- Thanks, though.
- What?
- Huh?
Here. I'll give you this,
so don't tell anyone I stole this.
What? You stole it?
Huh?
I thought you saw me.
What? Hey!
Ah, you dropped something.
Hey!
Shall we postpone the viewing
to another day?
Yes.
You're not leaving?
Well, I got curious.
About Genichi and Mr. Sakuta?
It's not exactly that
I want those two to break up.
That being said, I don't really understand
Mr. Hatano and the others.
- I get you.
- What?
Oh,
I can relate for not understanding them.
All kinds of people come to me.
By that, I really mean all kinds.
But, well, that’s what makes
my job interesting.
I'll take my leave now.
- Bye.
Here you go.
RESERVATION SLIP
- Please wait a moment.
- Okay.
- Is this the item you reserved?
- Yes.
How’s this apartment? Do you like it?
Do you live here too, Ms. Inokashira?
I live alone, just behind here.
But you're not alone, right?
You're right.
It might be too lively
to really call it living alone.
People who aren't married
are called "single", right?
Being single or currently living alone?
Yes.
I’m alone too.
Same, me too!
But you’re not really alone.
Yeah.
I want to aim for that too.
Me?
Make sure you reconcile properly.
Adults shouldn’t sulk like this.
Sorry for the wait.
Can you hold this for me?
Okay.
It looks delicious!
Sorry, that's meant to be taken elsewhere.
To where?
Weren’t you looking forward to it?
I already have something else
to look forward to.
Even more so than Christmas cake
or New Year’s food.
Something much exciting.
Hey, wait up!
Shut up!
How long are you going to follow me?
That’s stealing! It’s a crime!
You dropped this!
- Ah, give that back!
- Huh?
Hey!
You’ll get arrested!
What?
People will think you’re a bad man!
Stones will be thrown at you
from people around you.
Who cares about that!
I’m doing things my way!
Ah, hey!
- What's this place?
- This is a facility
where I grew up until high school.
CHILDREN’S HOME: HOSHINOOKA HOUSE
If you'd like,
please share this with everyone.
- Are you sure? Thanks.
- Of course.
They’ll love it!
And they are?
Let me introduce them.
Kanata and Micchan are fighting!
- Yume spilled her juice!
- Not again…
Sorry, can you wait a moment?
- We’ll return another time then.
- Oh, but…
I came by to pass you this cake.
Sorry about this.
I'll see you again
when it's not so chaotic.
- Yes.
- I'm so sorry.
Hey, Kanata.
- Come on now. Give that back.
- GIve it back!
- It's mine!
- No…
I'll try singing.
I, I have a dream
A dream of you and me
We're flying high above
We're soaring over the sea
Bless me, bless me with wings
For I, so want to fly
These precious white wings
Will take me soaring high
To the sun that lights the day
To the clouds that drift away
Only then will I be free
Past the city lights and haze
Through the autumn trees ablaze
In the sky I am truly free
Just you and me
This is the song everyone sang for me
when I left this facility.
You said it would help me understand
my feelings if I sang, Hatano.
How did you feel?
I’m excited.
Excited?
The life at the facility was lively,
and everyone got along.
We weren’t family,
but it felt like we really were.
Still, by the rules at the time,
we had to leave
once we graduated high school.
When I left, I bawled my eyes out.
That’s how much I loved…
this place.
So, I thought that someday
I’d want to make a home like this myself.
I knew it’d be tough since I’m gay.
But even so…
You know, to tell the truth,
I was a little…
thrilled…
when you said let's buy a house
and make it our "clamp".
Even now,
the fact that you're seriously
trying to buy a house
makes me happy.
More than I’ve ever been
about any other reservation.
I'm really looking forward to it!
I'm sorry.
I won’t say anything
like "let’s break up" anymore.
Let’s buy…
a house for us both!
What do you want?
To reconcile.
No, I don't want to do that here.
No one’s watching.
There’s something I want you to see.
What is it?
- I’ll come to your room later.
- Okay.
I wonder what it is…
Who knows?
What's that?
"I didn’t really understand
you two at all,
but it was incredibly interesting.
So, please get along with each other."
It's from Ms. Matsu.
What?
Um, how about writing something like this
in the notarized contract?
- What?
- "Even if we don’t understand each other,
let’s enjoy it…
and get along."
Okay.
After the beep tone,
please leave your name and message.
Hello.
Mom, guess what?
MOM
I tried making a guitar out of cardboard…
but it turned out weird.
I’m not even sure if it’s a guitar or not.
NARA PICKLES
Things that are between
guitar and not-guitar.
family and not-family.
Things that are between
parent and not-parent.
There are so many things without names.
There we go!
One more left.
SAITAMA, AICHI, FUKUSHIMA…
But even those things
can be just as important as the ones
that have names, right?
PARTY B & C WILL SUPPORT PARTY A’S DREAM
Mom--
The recording time has ended.
Please come home soon…
Shall I
take a picture for you?
- What?
- Over there.
Say cheese!
Thank you.
- Here you go!
- Thank you.
That's hilarious.
What?
Huh?
NARA SOUVENIR, DEER CRACKERS
You made it?
Yes.
- Can I play it?
- Yes.
You're a genius.
Yeah.
It really looks like a guitar!
It’s really cute.
Was this really
your first time making one?
Yes. Even if I end up
in a child guidance center,
I want to be someone who makes guitars.
Yeah, you definitely can! I know you can.
You made something this amazing after all.
Wait, did you decide the shape yourself?
- Yes. Also…
- Hey.
everyone drew on it too.
- You’ve got talent for this.
- Hey, I said!
There's a rabbit.
It’s gone!
The 30 million yen…
What?
CHASU, CHAN
Subtitle translation by: Jeffery